

#### Contact

phone +31622040319 email info@arejo.nl

location The Hague, Netherlands github github

portfolio portfolio linkedin LinkedIn

#### About me

#### Startup founder turned developer.

Extremely passionate about building beautiful, practical and smart things. Self-starting, highly determined, obsessively persistent.

Having completed the Front-end section of the Full-Stack Career Course on **codecademy**, I am eager to practice my new found skills as a Front-end / React Developer.

Open for a junior position or Freelance assignment. Remote / hybrid preferred.
Get in touch!

#### Kev Skills

Building web-apps from start to finish Rocking React & Redux

## Tech Skills

HTML
CSS
JavaScript
React
Redux
Node.js
Express.js
SQL
Git
GitHub
TDD

Mocha JEST

React Testing Library

JSON

## **Marketing Skills**

Google Analytics
Goal Tracking
Growth Hacking Principles
Split Testing
Conversion Optimalisation
Google Adwords
Facebook Ads

## Additional Skills

Adobe Creative Suite Google Sketchup SCRUM Agile

## Experience

2021 - Current Arejas The Hague Becoming a Full-Stack JavaScript Developer Bootcamp on Codecademy, Studying React / Express. Build and sold a campervan to be able to study fulltime. See: Education / About me.

2019/2022 Freelance Developer

Arejas Wordpress websites &
The Hague Weing Divi Elementer

Wordpress websites & webshops for different clients using Divi, Elementor, WooCommerce, HTML and CSS

2010-2019 mijnJohan.nl

privately held Development, Marketing and Sales. Homegrown accountancy software for independent entrepreneurs.

Passive Income Company.

2017 Growth Hacker

2016-2017 Camptoo.nl The Hague

Head responsible for the growth of the productoffering for this peer-2-peer Campers & Caravans renting platform, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

2015-2016 First marketing Officer
Yippie.nl Head responsible for the

Head responsible for the first growth spurt in users of this shopping-app, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Facebook Ads, Google Ads, Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

2011-2014 OWNR The Hague Startup Founder
Internet startup in action sports. Responsible for marketing, sales, investors, product-development and allround succes. Collaborations with among

others: Quiksilver / DC shoes and Nitro Snowboards.

## **Education**

2021 - Present codecademy

Full-Stack Developer Career Path Course
Becoming a Full-Stack web developer learning to
build web-apps' front-end and back-end using HTML,

CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, SQL, TDD, Mocha, Jest, React Testing Library, Markdown, JSON, Git & Github.

JSON, GIL &

2020 - 2021 codecademy Build a back-end app with JavaScript

A predecessor to codecademy's back-end engineer career path. This was my introduction to JavaScript, Node, Express, SQL and building API's.

2008-2010 Creative Advertising

WdKa Art Direction, concept

Rotterdam of Petrodom

Art Direction, concepting & realisation. Arts Academy

of Rotterdam.

1998-2004 Ashram College Alphen aan den Rijn Atheneum

Atheneum. Focus on Economics & Society. Field of choice: Computer Science. Research paper: Encryption.

# Certifications

• Back-end app with Javascript | Write API's with Node, Express & SQL | Codecademy | Jan '21

## Languages

Dutch English German Spanish

## Hobbies

Snowboard Skateboard Surf Wake Climbing Guitar Travel Campervans